{"_id":{"$oid":"5eba527af5210100176d7aa9"},"options":["start()","system()","main()","printf()"],"question":"Which is the only function all C programs must contain?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eba5552f5210100176d7aaa"},"options":["Operator","Function","Macro","None of these"],"question":"What is sizeof() in C?","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eba5664f5210100176d7aab"},"options":["1","2","No Limit","Depends on Compiler"],"question":"How many main() function we can have in our project?","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eba56cff5210100176d7aad"},"options":["-3.4e38 to 3.4e38","-32767 to 32768","-32668 to 32667","-32768 to 32767"],"question":"For 16-bit compiler allowable range for integer constants is ________?","answer":{"$numberInt":"3"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eba5709f5210100176d7aae"},"options":["30","32","24","36"],"question":"Standard ANSI C recognizes ______ number of keywords?","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eba5781f5210100176d7aaf"},"options":["auto","case","main","default"],"question":"Which one of the following is not a reserved keyword for C?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eba57d2f5210100176d7ab0"},"options":["A number","A special symbol other than underscore","Both of the above","An alphabet"],"question":"A C variable cannot start with","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eba582ff5210100176d7ab1"},"options":["start()","system()","main()","printf()"],"question":"Which is the only function all C programs must contain?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eba5885f5210100176d7ab2"},"options":["float","real","int","double"],"question":"Which of the following is not a correct variable type?","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eba5921f5210100176d7ab3"},"options":["Both can occur multiple times, but a declaration must occur first","A definition occurs once, but a declaration may occur many times","Both can occur multiple           times, but a definition must occur first","A declaration occurs once, but a definition may occur many times"],"question":"What is the difference between a declaration and a definition of a variable?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eba5964f5210100176d7ab4"},"options":["Yes","No","Depends on compiler","None of the above"],"question":"Nesting of if-else statements is allowed in C Programming.","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eba5998f5210100176d7ab5"},"options":["True","False","Depends on compiler","None of the above"],"question":"A char variable storing either an ASCII character or a Unicode character is allowed inside switch case.","answer":{"$numberInt":"3"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eba59c6f5210100176d7ab6"},"options":["False","True","Depends on compiler","None of the above"],"question":"We cannot use String in the Switch case as label !","answer":{"$numberInt":"3"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eba59f7f5210100176d7ab7"},"options":["Character","Integer","Enum","Float"],"question":"Which of the following cannot be checked in a switch case statement ?","answer":{"$numberInt":"3"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eba5a22f5210100176d7ab8"},"options":["No","Yes","Depends on the Compiler","None of the above"],"question":"Continue statement is allowed inside the switch case statement ?","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eba5a44f5210100176d7ab9"},"options":["If","Break","Continue","exit"],"question":"Which of the statement we need to write , in order to check any condition.","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eba5a6df5210100176d7aba"},"options":["for","do-while","while","switch"],"question":"Which of the following is not an example of looping statement ?","answer":{"$numberInt":"3"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eba5c98f5210100176d7abc"},"options":["Function Controlled Loop","Entry Controlled Loop","None of these","Exit Controlled Loop"],"question":"For loop is _________.","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eba626af5210100176d7abe"},"options":[" All are helpful in defining new variables"," All are helpful in defining new data types"," All are helpful in defining new pointers"," All are helpful in defining new structures"],"question":"Similarity between a structure, union and enumeration,","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eba62e9f5210100176d7abf"},"options":["0","2","1","Error"],"question":"What value strcmp() function returns when two strings are the same?","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eba7b7349bc8f0017c8d759"},"options":["* (asterisk)","| (pipeline)","- (hyphen)","_ (underscore)"],"question":"Which of the following special symbol allowed in a variable name?","answer":{"$numberInt":"3"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eba7beb49bc8f0017c8d75a"},"options":["ceil(1.66)","floor(1.66)","roundup(1.66)","roundto(1.66)"],"question":"How would you round off a value from 1.66 to 2.0?","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eba7c5049bc8f0017c8d75b"},"options":["float","double","long double","far double"],"question":"By default a real number is treated as a","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eba7daa49bc8f0017c8d75c"},"options":["Defining","Declaring","Prototyping","Calling"],"question":"When we mention the prototype of a function?,","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eba81c049bc8f0017c8d75d"},"options":["2","3","4","1"],"question":"How many loops are there in C,","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eba824a49bc8f0017c8d75e"},"options":["Operator Overloading","Function Overloading","Function Overriding","Function renaming"],"question":"The concept of two functions with same name is known as?","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eba82b449bc8f0017c8d75f"},"options":["math.h","mathio.h","string.h","ctype.h"],"question":"What is the following is invalid header file in C?","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eba834b49bc8f0017c8d760"},"options":["stdio.h","conio.h","stdlib.h","stdlibio.h"],"question":"Library function getch() belongs to which header file?","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eba83b149bc8f0017c8d761"},"options":["mathio.h","math.h","square.h","stdio.h"],"question":"Library function pow() belongs to which header file?","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5eba840a49bc8f0017c8d762"},"options":["Yes","No","Depends on Compiler","Yes but run time error"],"question":"Can we declare function inside structure of C Programming?","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaa13883adf600179e2df6"},"options":["Directory","Data Bank","Meta Data","None of the above"],"question":"Data about data is normally termed as:","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaa64e83adf600179e2dfc"},"options":["A number of tuples","A number of attributes","A number of tables","A number of constraints"],"question":"In the relational model, cardinality is termed as:","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaa6cf83adf600179e2dfd"},"options":["Procedural language","Non- Procedural language","Data definition language","High-level language"],"question":"Relational calculus is a","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaa6eb83adf600179e2dfe"},"options":["Conceptual view","Internal view","External view","Physical View"],"question":"The view of total database content is","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaa71283adf600179e2dff"},"options":["a Unary operator","a Binary operator","a Ternary operator","not defined"],"question":"Cartesian product in relational algebra is","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaa74183adf600179e2e00"},"options":["Description of the logical structure of a database.","The addition of new structures in the database system.","Manipulation & processing of the database.","Definition of a physical structure of the database system."],"question":"DML is provided for","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaabe983adf600179e2e01"},"options":["Selection operation","Rename operation","Join operation","Projection operation"],"question":"‘AS’ clause is used in SQL for","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaac0b83adf600179e2e02"},"options":["Object Database Connectivity","Oral Database Connectivity","Oracle Database Connectivity","Open Database Connectivity"],"question":"ODBC stands for","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaac4f83adf600179e2e03"},"options":["two levels","four levels","three levels","one level"],"question":"Architecture of the database can be viewed as","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaac9083adf600179e2e04"},"options":["Tuples","Attributes","Tables","Rows"],"question":"In a relational model, relations are termed as","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaacd183adf600179e2e05"},"options":["HLL","DML","DDL","DCL"],"question":"The database schema is written in","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaad0783adf600179e2e06"},"options":["physical level","logical level","conceptual level","view level"],"question":"In the architecture of a database system external level is the","answer":{"$numberInt":"3"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaad2f83adf600179e2e07"},"options":["strong entity set","weak entity set","simple entity set","primary entity set"],"question":"An entity set that does not have sufficient attributes to form a primary key is a","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaad5b83adf600179e2e08"},"options":["Graph","List","Links","Tree"],"question":"In Hierarchical model records are organised as","answer":{"$numberInt":"3"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaad7383adf600179e2e09"},"options":["rectangle","square","ellipse","triangle"],"question":"In an E-R diagram attributes are represented by","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaad9883adf600179e2e0a"},"options":["not Null","Null","both Null & not Null","any value"],"question":"In case of entity integrity, the primary key may be","answer":{"$numberInt":"3"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaadbd83adf600179e2e0b"},"options":["DML","DDL","VDL","SDL"],"question":"The language used in application programs to request data from the DBMS is referred to as the","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaade383adf600179e2e0c"},"options":["is the entire database","is a standard way of organising information into accessible parts","describes how data is actually stored on disk","both (A) and (C)"],"question":"A logical schema","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaae0a83adf600179e2e0d"},"options":["data file","data record","menu","bank"],"question":"Related fields in a database are grouped to form a","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaae3b83adf600179e2e0e"},"options":["users","separate files","database","database administrator"],"question":"The database environment has all of the following components except:","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaae5d83adf600179e2e0f"},"options":["module","relational model","schema","subschema"],"question":"The way a particular application views the data from the database that the application uses is a","answer":{"$numberInt":"3"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaae8983adf600179e2e10"},"options":["rectangle","ellipse","diamond box","circle"],"question":"In an E-R diagram an entity set is represented by a","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebae3bf1848f30017d6ae40"},"options":["module","relational model","schema","subschema"],"question":"The way a particular application views the data from the database that the application uses is a","answer":{"$numberInt":"3"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebae3f61848f30017d6ae41"},"options":["rectangle","ellipse","diamond box","circle"],"question":"In an E-R diagram an entity set is represented by a","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebae4171848f30017d6ae42"},"options":["update files","print files on paper","data entry","delete files"],"question":"A report generator is used to","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebae43c1848f30017d6ae43"},"options":["It is an integrated collection of logically related records.","It consolidates separate files into a common pool of data records.","Data stored in a database is independent of the application programs using it.","All of the above"],"question":"The property/properties of a database is/are:","answer":{"$numberInt":"3"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebae4601848f30017d6ae44"},"options":["The data definition language (DDL)","The data manipulation language (DML)","The database administrator (DBA)","A query language"],"question":"The DBMS language component which can be embedded in a program is","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebae4811848f30017d6ae45"},"options":["Criteria","a relation","a tuple","an attribute"],"question":"A relational database developer refers to a record as","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebae4a21848f30017d6ae46"},"options":["is no need for primary key data","is much more data independence than some other database models","are explicit relationships among records","are tables with many dimensions"],"question":"The relational model feature is that there","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebae4be1848f30017d6ae47"},"options":["the logical view","the physical view","the external view","all of the above"],"question":"A subschema expresses","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5eba506bf5210100176d7aa8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaf7a11848f30017d6ae68"},"options":["physical address and logical address","port address","specific address","all of the mentioned"],"question":"Which address is used in an internet employing the TCP/IP protocols?","answer":{"$numberInt":"3"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebaf4c01848f30017d6ae66"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaf7c61848f30017d6ae69"},"options":["physical address","logical address","port address","specific address"],"question":"Which address identifies a process on a host?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebaf4c01848f30017d6ae66"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaf7dc1848f30017d6ae6a"},"options":["network layer","physical layer","data link layer","transport layer"],"question":"Transmission data rate is decided by","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebaf4c01848f30017d6ae66"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaf7f91848f30017d6ae6b"},"options":["computer network","distributed system","both (a) and (b)","none of the mentioned"],"question":"When collection of various computers seems a single coherent system to its client, then it is called","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebaf4c01848f30017d6ae66"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaf81a1848f30017d6ae6c"},"options":["a process in one device is able to exchange information with a process in another device","a process is running on both devices","PIDs of the processes running of different devices are same","none of the mentioned"],"question":"Two devices are in network if","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebaf4c01848f30017d6ae66"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaf8301848f30017d6ae6d"},"options":["prior network","chief network","prime network","overlay network"],"question":"Which one of the following computer network is built on the top of another network?","answer":{"$numberInt":"3"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebaf4c01848f30017d6ae66"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaf8421848f30017d6ae6e"},"options":["the computer that originates the data","the computer that routes the data","the computer that terminates the data","all of the mentioned"],"question":"In computer network nodes are","answer":{"$numberInt":"3"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebaf4c01848f30017d6ae66"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaf8521848f30017d6ae6f"},"options":["personal area network","local area network","virtual private network","none of the mentioned"],"question":"Bluetooth is an example of","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebaf4c01848f30017d6ae66"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaf8641848f30017d6ae70"},"options":["bridge","firewall"," router","all of the above"],"question":" A _____ is a device that forwards packets between networks by processing the routing information included in the packet.","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebaf4c01848f30017d6ae66"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaf8741848f30017d6ae71"},"options":["protocol architecture","protocol stack","protocol suit","none of the mentioned"],"question":"A list of protocols used by a system, one protocol per layer, is called","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebaf4c01848f30017d6ae66"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaf8891848f30017d6ae72"},"options":["Syntax","Semantics","Struct',None of the mentioned"],"question":"The structure or format of data is called","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebaf4c01848f30017d6ae66"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaf89c1848f30017d6ae73"},"options":["Automatic","Half-duplex","Full-duplex","Simplex"],"question":"Communication between a computer and a keyboard involves ______________ transmission","answer":{"$numberInt":"3"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebaf4c01848f30017d6ae66"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaf8b01848f30017d6ae74"},"options":["CNNET","NSFNET","ASAPNET","ARPANET"],"question":"The first Network was","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebaf4c01848f30017d6ae66"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaf8c11848f30017d6ae75"},"options":["path","Medium","Protocol","Route"],"question":"The _______ is the physical path over which a message travels.","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebaf4c01848f30017d6ae66"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaf8d31848f30017d6ae76"},"options":["PC","Smartphones","Servers","Switch"],"question":"Which of this is not a network edge device?","answer":{"$numberInt":"3"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebaf4c01848f30017d6ae66"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaf8e41848f30017d6ae77"},"options":["Protocols","Standards","RFCs","None of the mentioned"],"question":"A set of rules that governs data communication","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebaf4c01848f30017d6ae66"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaf8f61848f30017d6ae78"},"options":["Unipoint","Multipoint","Point to point","None of the mentioned"],"question":"Three or more devices share a link in ________ connection.","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebaf4c01848f30017d6ae66"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaf9431848f30017d6ae79"},"options":["Application layer","Session layer","Transport layer","Link layer"],"question":"Delimiting and synchronization of data exchange is provided by","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebaf4c01848f30017d6ae66"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaf95e1848f30017d6ae7a"},"options":["physical","IP","port","specific"],"question":"The_____ address identifies a process on a host.","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebaf4c01848f30017d6ae66"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaf9711848f30017d6ae7b"},"options":["physical","IP","port","specific"],"question":"The ____ address uniquely defines a host on the Internet.","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebaf4c01848f30017d6ae66"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebaf9891848f30017d6ae7c"},"options":["physical","IP","port","specific"],"question":"The ________ address, also known as the link address, is the address of a node as defined by its LAN or WAN.","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebaf4c01848f30017d6ae66"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebafbda1848f30017d6ae7d"},"options":["physical","IP","port","specific"],"question":"The ________ address, also known as the link address, is the address of a node as defined by its LAN or WAN.","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebaf4c01848f30017d6ae66"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebafc681848f30017d6ae7e"},"options":["physical","data link","network","none of the above"],"question":"The ______ layer adds a header to the packet coming from the upper layer that includes the logical addresses of the sender and receiver.","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebaf4c01848f30017d6ae66"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebafca41848f30017d6ae7f"},"options":["physical","data link","network","none of the above"],"question":"The ______ layer is responsible for moving frames from one hop (node) to the next.","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebaf4c01848f30017d6ae66"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebafcc01848f30017d6ae80"},"options":["32","64","128","variable"],"question":"IPv6 has _______ -bit addresses.","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebaf4c01848f30017d6ae66"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebafcd31848f30017d6ae81"},"options":["Physical","Data link","Transport","None of the above"],"question":"The _______ layer changes bits into electromagnetic signals.","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebaf4c01848f30017d6ae66"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebafce41848f30017d6ae82"},"options":["Physical","Data link","Network","Transport"],"question":"The _______ layer is the layer closest to the transmission medium.","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebaf4c01848f30017d6ae66"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebafcfb1848f30017d6ae83"},"options":["Network","Transport","Application","Physical"],"question":"The process-to-process delivery of the entire message is the responsibility of the _______ layer.","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebaf4c01848f30017d6ae66"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebafd0b1848f30017d6ae84"},"options":["Medium","Protocol","Message","Transmission"],"question":"The information to be communicated in a data communications system is the _______.","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebaf4c01848f30017d6ae66"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebafd281848f30017d6ae85"},"options":["Performance","Reliability","Security","Feasibility"],"question":"Frequency of failure and network recovery time after a failure are measures of the _______ of a network.","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebaf4c01848f30017d6ae66"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebafd5c1848f30017d6ae86"},"options":["simplex","half-duplex","full-duplex","automatic"],"question":"Communication between a computer and a keyboard involves ______________ transmission.","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebaf4c01848f30017d6ae66"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebba465404a9a0017b7efa5"},"options":["-128 to 127","-32768 to 32767","-2147483648 to 2147483647","None of the mentioned"],"question":"What is the range of data type short in Java?","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebba3d9404a9a0017b7efa4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebba4a7404a9a0017b7efa6"},"options":["-128 to 127","-32768 to 32767","-2147483648 to 2147483647","None of the mentioned"],"question":"What is the range of data type byte in Java?","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebba3d9404a9a0017b7efa4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebba4ba404a9a0017b7efa7"},"options":["int","long","byte","float"],"question":"An expression involving byte, int, and literal numbers is promoted to which of these?","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebba3d9404a9a0017b7efa4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebba4ca404a9a0017b7efa8"},"options":["1.7e-308","3.4e-038","1.7e+308","3.4e-050"],"question":"Which of these literals can be contained in a data type float variable?","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebba3d9404a9a0017b7efa4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebba4e2404a9a0017b7efa9"},"options":["int","float","double","long"],"question":"Which data type value is returned by all transcendental math functions?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebba3d9404a9a0017b7efa4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebba4f4404a9a0017b7efaa"},"options":["-128 to 127","0 to 256","0 to 32767","0 to 65535"],"question":"What is the numerical range of a char in Java?","answer":{"$numberInt":"3"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebba3d9404a9a0017b7efa4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebba507404a9a0017b7efab"},"options":["ASCII","ISO-LATIN-1","UNICODE","None of the mentioned"],"question":"Which of these coding types is used for data type characters in Java?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebba3d9404a9a0017b7efa4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebba515404a9a0017b7efac"},"options":["True & False","0 & 1","Any integer value","Both a & b"],"question":"Which of these values can a boolean variable contain?","answer":{"$numberInt":"3"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebba3d9404a9a0017b7efa4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebba529404a9a0017b7efad"},"options":["boolean b1 = 1;","boolean b2 = ‘false’;","boolean b3 = false;","boolean b4 = ‘true’"],"question":"Which one is a valid declaration of a boolean?","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebba3d9404a9a0017b7efa4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebba53e404a9a0017b7efae"},"options":["objects","object references","primitive data type","None of the above"],"question":"In Java Arrays are:","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebba3d9404a9a0017b7efa4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebba55f404a9a0017b7efaf"},"options":["Bytecode is executed by JVM","The applet makes the Java code secure and portable","Use of exception handling","Dynamic binding between objects"],"question":" Which of the following option leads to the portability and security of Java?","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebba3d9404a9a0017b7efa4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebba57e404a9a0017b7efb0"},"options":["Dynamic","Architecture Neutral","Use of pointers","Object-oriented"],"question":"Which of the following is not a Java features?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebba3d9404a9a0017b7efa4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebba5a1404a9a0017b7efb1"},"options":["Unicode escape sequence","Octal escape","Hexadecimal","Line feed"],"question":"The ! article referred to as a","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebba3d9404a9a0017b7efa4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebba5b8404a9a0017b7efb2"},"options":["JVM","JRE","JDK","JDB"],"question":"_____ is used to find and fix bugs in the Java programs.","answer":{"$numberInt":"3"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebba3d9404a9a0017b7efa4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebba736404a9a0017b7efb4"},"options":["Object","int","long","void"],"question":"What is the return type of the hashCode() method in the Object class?","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebba3d9404a9a0017b7efa4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebba75c404a9a0017b7efb5"},"options":["ABH8097","L990023","904423","0xnf029L"],"question":"Which of the following is a valid long literal?","answer":{"$numberInt":"3"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebba3d9404a9a0017b7efa4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebba80a404a9a0017b7efb6"},"options":["0","Not a Number","Infinity","Run time exception"],"question":"What does the expression float a = 35 / 0 return?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebba3d9404a9a0017b7efa4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebba826404a9a0017b7efb7"},"options":["javap tool","javaw command","Javadoc tool","javah command"],"question":"Which of the following tool is used to generate API documentation in HTML format from doc comments in source code?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebba3d9404a9a0017b7efa4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebba83f404a9a0017b7efb8"},"options":["Serialization","Variable Shadowing","Abstraction","Multi-threading"],"question":"In which process, a local variable has the same name as one of the instance variables?","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebba3d9404a9a0017b7efa4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebba85f404a9a0017b7efb9"},"options":["It has only methods","Objects can't be created","It has a fixed class name","It has no class name"],"question":"Which of the following is true about the anonymous inner class?","answer":{"$numberInt":"4"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebba3d9404a9a0017b7efa4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebba877404a9a0017b7efba"},"options":["java.util package","java.lang package","java.awt package","java.io package"],"question":"Which package contains the Random class?","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebba3d9404a9a0017b7efa4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebba89b404a9a0017b7efbb"},"options":["An object created by using the new keyword.","An object of a superclass created in the subclass.","An object without having any name but having a reference.","An object that has no reference."],"question":"What do you mean by nameless objects?","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebba3d9404a9a0017b7efa4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebba8c4404a9a0017b7efbc"},"options":["Runnable Interface","Marker Interface","Abstract Interface","CharSequence Interface"],"question":"An interface with no fields or methods is known as a ______.","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebba3d9404a9a0017b7efa4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebba8e6404a9a0017b7efbd"},"options":["Applet class","Window class","Frame class","Dialog class"],"question":"Which of the following is an immediate subclass of the Panel class?","answer":{"$numberInt":"3"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebba3d9404a9a0017b7efa4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebba900404a9a0017b7efbe"},"options":["RuntimeException and Error class","Exception and VirtualMachineError class","Error and Exception class","IOException and VirtualMachineError class"],"question":"Which of these classes are the direct subclasses of the Throwable class?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebba3d9404a9a0017b7efa4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebba915404a9a0017b7efbf"},"options":["Stack","String memory","Heap memory","Random storage space"],"question":"In which memory a String is stored, when we create a string using new operator?","answer":{"$numberInt":"4"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebba3d9404a9a0017b7efa4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebba936404a9a0017b7efc0"},"options":["It returns the existing string from memory","It creates a new string in the database","It modifies the existing string in the database","None of the above"],"question":"What is the use of the intern() method?","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebba3d9404a9a0017b7efa4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebbe9a67314c3001764eb38"},"options":["Hyper Text Markup Language","High Text Markup Language","Hyper Tabular Markup Language","None of these"],"question":"HTML stands for?","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebbea0f7314c3001764eb39"},"options":["<TD>","<br>","<P>","<TR>"],"question":"Which of the following tag is used to mark a begining of paragraph?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebbead37314c3001764eb3b"},"options":["<LL>","<DD>","<DL>","<DS>"],"question":"From which tag descriptive list starts ?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebbeb3b7314c3001764eb3c"},"options":["<head>","<h6>","<heading>","<h1>"],"question":"Correct HTML tag for the largest heading is","answer":{"$numberInt":"3"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebbebaa7314c3001764eb3d"},"options":["Method","Action","Both (a)&(b)","None of these"],"question":"The attribute of <form> tag","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebbee497314c3001764eb3e"},"options":["No, there is no such terms as Empty Elements","Empty elements are element with no data","No, it is not valid to use Empty Element","None of these"],"question":"What are Empty elements and is it valid?","answer":"1","topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":"0"}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebbf4a47314c3001764eb3f"},"options":["size","len","maxlength","all of these"],"question":"Which of the following attributes of text box control allow to limit the maximum character?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebbf4fa7314c3001764eb40"},"options":["<Body>","<Title>","<HTML>","<Form>"],"question":"Web pages starts with which ofthe following tag?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebbf5677314c3001764eb41"},"options":["SGMT","SGML","SGMD","None of these"],"question":"HTML is a subset of","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebbf5d67314c3001764eb42"},"options":["<SELECT>","<BODY>","<INPUT>","Both (a) and (b)"],"question":"Which of the following is a container?","answer":{"$numberInt":"3"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebbf62e7314c3001764eb43"},"options":["REL","URL","REV","all of these"],"question":"The attribute, which define the relationship between current document and HREF'ed URL is","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebbf68d7314c3001764eb44"},"options":["line of text","full paragraph","word","request"],"question":"<DT> tag is designed to fit a single line of our web page but <DD> tag will accept a","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebbf7187314c3001764eb45"},"options":["method used to represent numbers in a character","method used to represent character in a number","a system that consists of a code which pairs each character with a pattern,sequence of natural numbers or electrical pulse in order to transmit the data","none of these"],"question":"Character encoding is","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebbfb607314c3001764eb46"},"options":["<LL>","<DD>","<DL>","<DS>"],"question":"From which tag the descriptive list starts?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebbfc767314c3001764eb47"},"options":["<TH>","<TD>","<TR>","<CAPTION>"],"question":"The tag which allows you to rest other HTML tags within the description is","answer":{"$numberInt":"3"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebbff1d7314c3001764eb48"},"options":["<HEAD>","<TITLE>","<BODY>","<FORM>"],"question":"<Base> tag is designed to appear only between","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebbffa77314c3001764eb49"},"options":["BASE element","HEAD element","both (a) and (b)","none of these"],"question":"A much better approach to establish the base URL is to use","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc001f7314c3001764eb4a"},"options":["<LI>","<DL>","<DD>","<UL>"],"question":"The tag used to create a new list item and also include a hyperlink is","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc00af7314c3001764eb4b"},"options":["No, they represent different elements altogether","Both are same","First is correct only","first is only correct"],"question":"Can the element <First> be replaced with <first>","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc011e7314c3001764eb4c"},"options":["rect","point","default","polygon"],"question":"Any part of the graphic that is not included in another hot zone is considered to be part of","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc01997314c3001764eb4d"},"options":["<LI>","<OL>","<LI> and <OL>","None of these"],"question":"Which of the tag is used to creates a number list?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc020d7314c3001764eb4e"},"options":["format tag","format tag","both (a) and (b)","None of these"],"question":"<INPUT> is","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc02877314c3001764eb4f"},"options":["CGI-BIN","RECYCLE-BIN","BIN","All of these"],"question":"The map definition file is generally stored in","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc03437314c3001764eb50"},"options":["<ISINDEX>","<A>","<LINK>","none of these"],"question":"The tag used to create a hypertext relationship between current document and another URL is","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc03a37314c3001764eb51"},"options":["<P> formatted text","<T> formatted text","<PRE> formatted text","none of these"],"question":"The text inside the <TEXT AREA> tag works like","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc048d7314c3001764eb52"},"options":["<TABLE>","<GROUP>","<DATA>","All of these"],"question":"Main container for <TR>, <TD> and <TH> is","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc04ef7314c3001764eb53"},"options":["Title tag","HEAD tag","EM tag","FORM tag"],"question":"The body tag usually used after","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc060a7314c3001764eb54"},"options":["<UL>","<OL>","<OT>","None of these"],"question":"Which tag creates a number/order list?","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc06657314c3001764eb55"},"options":["#","$","&","^"],"question":"Symbol used at the beginning of the HREF text is","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc06da7314c3001764eb56"},"options":["<_person>","<123 person>","Both (a) and (b)","None of these"],"question":"Which of the following is a Valid Name?","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc14b0e0640f0017f79f7b"},"options":["pointer","default","arrow","arr"],"question":"If we want to show an Arrow as cursor, then which value we will use ?","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc150ae0640f0017f79f7c"},"options":["border-color","border-decoration","border-style","border-line"],"question":"If we want to use a nice looking green dotted border around an image, which css property will we use?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc1576e0640f0017f79f7d"},"options":["empty-cell","blank-cell","noncontent-cell","void-cell"],"question":"Which of the following properties will we use to display border around a cell without any content ?","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc15dce0640f0017f79f7e"},"options":["640 pixels","100%","full-screen","1024 px"],"question":"What should be the table width, so that the width of a table adjust to the current width of the browser window?","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc16b4e0640f0017f79f7f"},"options":["Id","div","class","span"],"question":"Which attribute can be added to many HTML / XHTML elements to identify them as a member of a specific group ?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebbcb5430de290017cf4dc8"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc295d9ae00c00174f314f"},"options":["Id","text","class","name"],"question":"If we want define style for an unique element, then which css selector will we use?","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc099b7314c3001764eb57"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc29d79ae00c00174f3150"},"options":["d-index","s-index","x-index","z-index"],"question":"Suppose we want to arragnge five nos. of DIVs so that DIV4 is placed above DIV1. Now, which css property will we use to control the order of stack?","answer":{"$numberInt":"3"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc099b7314c3001764eb57"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc2a5e9ae00c00174f3151"},"options":["wrap","push","float","align"],"question":"If we want to wrap a block of text around an image, which css property will we use ?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc099b7314c3001764eb57"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc2ac89ae00c00174f3152"},"options":["pointer","default","arrow","arr"],"question":"If we want to show an Arrow as cursor, then which value we will use ?","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc099b7314c3001764eb57"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc2b2b9ae00c00174f3153"},"options":["border-color","border-decoration","border-style","border-line"],"question":"If we want to use a nice looking green dotted border around an image, which css property will we use?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc099b7314c3001764eb57"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc2b9d9ae00c00174f3154"},"options":["empty-cell","blank-cell","noncontent-cell","void-cell"],"question":"Which of the following properties will we use to display border around a cell without any content ?","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc099b7314c3001764eb57"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc30fc78213a001774b0a7"},"options":["wrap","push","float","align"],"question":"If we want to wrap a block of text around an image, which css property will we use?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc099b7314c3001764eb57"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc316778213a001774b0a8"},"options":["pointer","default","arrow","arr"],"question":"If we want to show an Arrow as cursor, then which value we will use ?","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc099b7314c3001764eb57"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc31c878213a001774b0a9"},"options":["border-color","border-decoration","border-style","border-line"],"question":"If we want to use a nice looking green dotted border around an image, which css property will we use?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc099b7314c3001764eb57"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc327278213a001774b0aa"},"options":["empty-cell","blank-cell","noncontent-cell","void-cell"],"question":"Which of the following properties will we use to display border around a cell without any content ?","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc099b7314c3001764eb57"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc372d78213a001774b0ab"},"options":["640 pixels","100%","full-screen","1024 px"],"question":"What should be the table width, so that the width of a table adjust to the current width of the browser window?","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc099b7314c3001764eb57"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc378278213a001774b0ac"},"options":["<src>","<link>","<style>","<css>"],"question":"Which element is used in the <HEAD> section on an HTML / XHTMLpage, if we want to use an external style sheet file to decorate the page ?","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc099b7314c3001764eb57"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc37ce78213a001774b0ad"},"options":["Id","div","class","span"],"question":"Which attribute can be added to many HTML / XHTML elements to identify them as a member of a specific group ?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc099b7314c3001764eb57"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc383078213a001774b0ae"},"options":["/* a comment */","// a comment //","/ a comment /","<' a comment'>"],"question":"How can we write comment along with CSS code ?","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc099b7314c3001764eb57"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc3f4f78213a001774b0af"},"options":["spacing","margin","padding","inner-margin"],"question":"Which css property you will use if you want to add some margin between a DIV's border and its inner text ?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc099b7314c3001764eb57"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc3fa078213a001774b0b0"},"options":["font-style","text-size","font-size","text-style"],"question":"Which CSS property is used to control the text size of an element ?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc099b7314c3001764eb57"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc402978213a001774b0b1"},"options":["fixed","absolute","inherit","relative"],"question":"The default value of position attribute is _________.","answer":{"$numberInt":"3"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc099b7314c3001764eb57"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc40b278213a001774b0b2"},"options":["p.all {color: red;}","p.all {color: #990000;}","all.p {color: #998877;}","p {color: red;}"],"question":"How will you make all paragraph elements 'RED' in color ?","answer":{"$numberInt":"3"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc099b7314c3001764eb57"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc415978213a001774b0b3"},"options":["a {text: no-underline;}","a {text-decoration:none;}","a {text-style: no-underline;}","a {text-decoration: no-underline;}"],"question":"By default Hyperlinks are displayed with an underline. How do you remove the underline from all hyperlinks by using CSS code ?","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc099b7314c3001764eb57"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc445578213a001774b0b5"},"options":["<javascript>","<scripted>","<script>","<js>"],"question":"What is the HTML tag under which one can write the JavaScript code?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc42fc78213a001774b0b4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc454578213a001774b0b6"},"options":["JavaScript variable names must begin with a letter or the underscore character.","JavaScript variable names are case sensitive.","Both of the above.","None of the above."],"question":"Which of the following is true about variable naming conventions in JavaScript?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc42fc78213a001774b0b4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc46cb78213a001774b0b7"},"options":["named function","anonymous function","Both of the above.","None of the above."],"question":"Which of the following is a valid type of function javascript supports?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc42fc78213a001774b0b4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc478078213a001774b0b8"},"options":["last()","get()","pop()","None of the above."],"question":"Which built-in method removes the last element from an array and returns that element?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc42fc78213a001774b0b4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc481678213a001774b0b9"},"options":["toLowerCase()","toLower()","changeCase(case)","None of the above."],"question":"Which built-in method returns the calling string value converted to lower case?","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc42fc78213a001774b0b4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc488d78213a001774b0ba"},"options":["toSource()","valueOf()","toString()","None of the above."],"question":"Which of the following function of Boolean object returns the primitive value of the Boolean object?","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc42fc78213a001774b0b4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc497d78213a001774b0bb"},"options":["slice()","split()","substr()","search()"],"question":"Which of the following function of String object returns the characters in a string beginning at the specified location through the specified number of characters?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc42fc78213a001774b0b4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc49eb78213a001774b0bc"},"options":["anchor()","big()","blink()","italics()"],"question":"Which of the following function of String object creates a string to blink as if it were in a <blink> tag?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc42fc78213a001774b0b4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc4a0978213a001774b0bd"},"options":["anchor()","big()","blink()","italics()"],"question":"Which of the following function of String object creates a string to blink as if it were in a <blink> tag?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc42fc78213a001774b0b4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc4a7c78213a001774b0be"},"options":["fixed()","fontcolor()","fontsize()","bold()"],"question":"Which of the following function of String object causes a string to be displayed in the specified size as if it were in a <font size = 'size'> tag?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc42fc78213a001774b0b4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc4b2778213a001774b0bf"},"options":["concat()","every()","filter()","some()"],"question":" Which of the following function of Array object creates a new array with all of the elements of this array for which the provided filtering function returns true?","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc42fc78213a001774b0b4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebc4cc478213a001774b0c0"},"options":["unshift()","sort()","splice()","toString()"],"question":"Which of the following function of Array object adds one or more elements to the front of an array and returns the new length of the array?","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc42fc78213a001774b0b4"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebd0a61e982a50017182514"},"options":["Both (i) and (ii)","Both (ii) and (iv)","Only (ii)","Both (i) and (iii)"],"question":"What does PHP stand for? i) Personal Home Page ii) Hypertext Preprocessor iii) Pretext Hypertext Processor iv) Preprocessor Home Page","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc4f3678213a001774b0c1"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebd0af9e982a50017182515"},"options":[".html",".xml",".php",".ph"],"question":"PHP files have a default file extension of.","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc4f3678213a001774b0c1"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebd0b7ae982a50017182516"},"options":["< php >","< ? php ?>","< ? ? >","< ?php ? >"],"question":"A PHP script should start with ___ and end with ___:","answer":{"$numberInt":"3"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc4f3678213a001774b0c1"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebd0c34e982a50017182517"},"options":["(i) and (ii)","(i), (ii) and (iii)","All of the mentioned","None of the mentioned"],"question":"Which of the looping statements is/are supported by PHP? i) for loop ii) while loop iii) do-while loop iv) foreach loop","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc4f3678213a001774b0c1"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebd0d5ce982a5001718251a"},"options":["Only (iv)","All of the mentioned.","(i), (ii) and (iii)","Only (iii)"],"question":" Which of the following is/are a PHP code editor? i) Notepad ii) Notepad++ iii) Adobe Dreamweaver iv) PDT","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc4f3678213a001774b0c1"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebd0eb8e982a5001718251b"},"options":["All of the mentioned.","Only (ii)","(ii) and (iii)","(ii), (iii) and (iv)"],"question":"Which of the following must be installed on your computer so as to run PHP script? i) Adobe Dreamweaver ii) PHP iii) Apache iv) IIS","answer":{"$numberInt":"3"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebc4f3678213a001774b0c1"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebd1992e982a50017182524"},"options":["Graph Oriented","Document Oriented","Key Value Pair","Column Based"],"question":"What kind of database MongoDB is?","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebd18f1e982a50017182523"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebd1a05e982a50017182525"},"options":["queryPlanner","executionStats","allPlansExecution","customExecutionStats"],"question":"Which is the default mode in which the explain() command runs?","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebd18f1e982a50017182523"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebd1a98e982a50017182526"},"options":["Compound Indexes","Multikey Indexes","Geospatial Indexes","All of the above"],"question":"Which type of indexes does MongoDB support?","answer":{"$numberInt":"3"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebd18f1e982a50017182523"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebd1b31e982a50017182527"},"options":["2 MB document and 100 MB RAM","2 MB document and no limit on RAM","16 MB document and 100 MB RAM"," No limit on document and 100 MB RAM"],"question":"Aggregation Pipelines have a limit of:","answer":{"$numberInt":"2"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebd18f1e982a50017182523"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebd1c0de982a50017182528"},"options":["$push","$wind","$wind.$wind","Can't be reversed"],"question":"Which of the following operators can reverse the effects of a double unwind operation?","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebd18f1e982a50017182523"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebd1c91e982a50017182529"},"options":["$","$elemMatch","$slice","Updating an array field without knowing its index is not possible."],"question":"The _______ operator can be used to identify an element in the array to be updated without explicitly specifying the position of the element.","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebd18f1e982a50017182523"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebd1df4e982a5001718252a"},"options":["frontend","backend","proprietary","All of the mentioned"],"question":"MongoDB has been adopted as ________ software by a number of major websites and services.","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebd18f1e982a50017182523"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebd1e4ce982a5001718252b"},"options":["SQL","Document databases","JSON","All of the mentioned"],"question":"Which of the following is a NoSQL Database Type ?","answer":{"$numberInt":"1"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebd18f1e982a50017182523"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebd1ebee982a5001718252c"},"options":["Cassandra","Riak","MongoDB","Redis"],"question":"Which of the following is a wide-column store ?","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebd18f1e982a50017182523"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5ebd1f1ae982a5001718252d"},"options":["collation","collection","heap","None of the mentioned"],"question":"Which of the following sorting is not supported by MongoDB ?","answer":{"$numberInt":"0"},"topic":{"$oid":"5ebd18f1e982a50017182523"},"__v":{"$numberInt":"0"}}
